achievementradio.com 2011-04-24

# Achievement Radio Network - Privacy Statement

#### **Achievement Radio Privacy Statement**

This site keeps all your personal information you give to _AchievementRadio.com_ secret. Your personal information is not shared with anyone else. Period. 

_Achievement Radio Network_ has created this privacy statement for _AchievementRadio.com_ in order to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy. The following statement discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site.

**AFFILIATE MARKETING DISCLAIMER - THE ADS ON THIS SITE ARE MY OWN ADS AND IF YOU MAKE A PURCHASE FROM THEM, I WILL RECEIVE A** **COMMISSION:** The “Site Sponsor” Ads on this site are my own ads from affiliate marketing relationships. If you make a purchase from them, I get a small commission. No, I don’t guarantee that if you buy any of these products that you will make X amount of money per month or per year! 

**Information Automatically Logged On AchievementRadio.com  
** This site may log your IP address to help diagnose problems with the web server and to administer this web site. This information is primarily used for general traffic tracking and security. 

**Cookies**   
This site uses cookies to track information about its visitors. This information includes the date/time of visits, pages viewed, and products ordered. 

**Order Forms  
** This site provides order forms for you to buy products. When you place an order, this site collects contact information (like your email address), and financial information (like your credit card number). Contact information from the order forms is used only to get in touch with you when necessary. This includes sending you the product(s) you ordered and contacting you if there's a problem with your order. Financial information that is collected is used to bill you for the order. 

**Newsletter**   
This site allows visitors to sign up for a free newsletter by providing an email address. The email address you provide is used only to send you the free newsletter, and you can unsubscribe by clicking a link in any issue of the newsletter. 

**External Links  
** This site contains links to other sites. This site and its owner(s) are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

**Public Forums  
** This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or newsgroups available to its visitors. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, so you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security  
** This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under its control. This site provides a secure server for all credit card orders, securely encrypting all personal data with industry-standard methods. This site does not store credit card numbers for processed orders.
